https://evanspetree.com/privacy-policy

AboutProfessionalsC. Michael Adams, Jr.Tommie A. BairdLouise Chandler BiedenharnBlake W. BourlandW. Kerby BowlingFrank N. Stockdale CarneyCharles W. ‘Chip’ Cavagnaro, Jr.David CockeL. Clayton Culpepper IIIBert A. Echols IIIPaul F. T. EdwardsRobert J. FehseR. Mark FieldElizabeth FriaryJoseph T. GetzRussell ‘Rusty’ J. HensleyNancy Hunt*Richard Hunt*James Stephen KingTheodore T. KitaiMichael R. MarshallJohn McQuiston IIJohn F. MurrahAaron J. NashCaren Beth NicholW. Lytle Nichol IVRichard E. M. Nichol, Jr.William L. Nichol VDavid C. PorteousAndrew H. RainesAndrew M. RainesWill RainesNaren Ravinootala*Daniel T. Robinson, Jr.Jerry Sanders*Ashby R. ScottDavid C. ScruggsJoel B. SklarRegan S. SteepletonHarley SteffensElizabeth ‘Beth’ StengelTyler G. TollisonE. Woods WeathersbyJohn David WilletM. Andrew WohlfarthBrian L. YoakumJacob C. ZweigPractice AreasAlternative Dispute ResolutionBanking / Commercial LendingConstruction and SuretyCorporate LawDebtor / Creditor LawEmployee BenefitsFamily Law / DivorceHealth Care LawInsolvencyIntellectual PropertyInternational Law / Foreign Direct InvestmentLabor and Employment LawLitigation / Dispute ResolutionPrivate ClientProperty TaxReal EstateTax, Trusts and Estate PlanningNewsContactAboutProfessionalsPractice AreasNewsContactDisclaimerPrivacy Privacy Policy
Your privacy is important to usPlease read the following Privacy Policy to understand what information Evans Petree receives based on your use of this web site and how that information will be treated. When you use this web site, you consent to Evans Petree’s use of your personal information in the manner specified in this Privacy Policy. This policy may be changed from time to time by us in response to changes in the type of information gathered through this site or in response to changes in applicable privacy laws.  Please check back from time to time.   This version of the policy was adopted in June 2011.Like all web site owners, Evans Petree has access to clickstream data that includes among other things, the IP address that you use to access our web site, which pages you visit, and what browser you used.  We do not collect any personally identifiable information from you (e.g., name, address, telephone number, e-mail address) unless you voluntarily choose to submit or otherwise disclose such information to us, including information submitted or disclosed by mail, telephone, fax, or electronically. While information gathered through this web site is accessible to various vendors providing services to our firm, such as our web site developer, hosting service provider, and information technology consultants, we will not sell, trade, or rent your personally identifiable information to third parties. Your information will only be used by us to respond to your request for information, to understand how you are accessing and using our web site so that we can try to improve our web site, and, if we accept an engagement to represent you, to assist us in providing legal services under the engagement.Our web site is not directed to children under thirteen (13) years of age.  If you are under eighteen (18), please consult with your parent or guardian about using this web site.Evans Petree is not obligated to monitor this web site or its use, or to retain the content of any user session. We reserve the right to do so, however, as we deem desireable for business or legal compliance purposes. We may use IP addresses to identify a user when we feel it is necessary to protect our service, web site, clients, potential clients, or others.This policy only addresses our use and disclosure of information we collect from you through this web site. To the extent that you disclose personal information to other web sites, you are subject to the privacy customs and policies of those other sites. We encourage you to ask questions before you disclose any personal information.Our Locations1715 Aaron Brenner Drive, Suite 800, Memphis, TN 38120 901.525.67811000 Ridgeway Loop Road, Suite 200, Memphis, TN 38120 901.525.67812550 Meridian Boulevard, Suite 200, Franklin, TN 37067 615.567.81611204 Office Park Drive, Unit B Oxford, MS 38655 662.546.4655Contact Us
EMAIL NOTICEThe mailing of this email is not intended to create, and receipt of it does not constitute an attorney-client relationship. Anything that you send to anyone at our Firm will not be confidential or privileged unless we have agreed to represent you. If you send this email, you confirm that you have read and understand this notice. Accept Decline
